{
    "id": "6d71fca933a049e2bd69d57fa436d79c",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Muslims fast in the month of Ramzan. Here fast is a/an ............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adjective",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the right man in the right place. Here right is a/an ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "pronoun",
                "adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There is not much truth in what he says. Here truth is a/an .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "adjective",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His theories are hard to understand. Here hard is a / an ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A little learning is a dangerous thing. Here dangerous is a/an ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "adjective",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Still waters run deep. Here waters is a/an ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "noun",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What annoys me most is his obstinacy. Here annoys is a/an ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "As he was ambitious, I felt that I shouldnâ€™t trust him. Here trust is a/an ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "adverb",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is like his father. Here like is a/an ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "conjunction",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not talk like that. Here that is a/an ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "pronoun",
                "adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}